<resources>
    <string name="app_name">tour_guide</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="weather_description">Saudi Arabia has a desert climate, with very high temperatures during the day and high at night in summer. In wintwer, Saudi Arabua - Riyadh gets low temperatures, 9 in average. For more, click the button bellow.</string>
    <string name="more">More...</string>


    <string name="first_event_title">The First Saudi State</string>
    <string name="first_event_desc">In early 1800\'s a Muslim scholar decided to move back to where now Saudi Arabia is and start the Muslim tradition and churches again. This created the first Saudi State because everyone had come back to the Muslim way.</string>
    <string name="first_event_date">Jan 1, 1800</string>
    <string name="second_event_title">The country of Saudi Arabia was made a country</string>
    <string name="second_event_desc">The country of Saudi Arabia was made a country and was called the Kindom of Saudi Arabia. The founder was Abd al-Aziz Al Saud. This day is celebrated with feasting and speeches.</string>
    <string name="second_event_date">Sep 23, 1932</string>
    <string name="third_event_title">Oil was Discovered</string>
    <string name="third_event_desc">The commercials for oil production started at the start of World War 2. The money from the oil helped the country provide free health care for everyone and education while not collecting taxes to pay for it. In 1998 the country\'s oil income dropped by 40% because of worldwide decline in prices.</string>
    <string name="third_event_date">Jan 1, 1936</string>
    <string name="fourth_event_title">Founding of Saudi Arabia Flag</string>
    <string name="fourth_event_desc">The flag of Saudi Arabia was made in 1973. The sword points to which way the flag is supposed to be hoisted. The Arabic writing says that there is no god but Allah, and that muhammad is his messenger. The green background is the Islamic color.</string>
    <string name="fourth_event_date">Mar 15, 1973</string>
</resources>
